{
    "id": "88728bd14bf54fabaf73afe1f88bcb6f",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You have been riding non-stop for hours. You ………………….. be very tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "can",
                "ought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… be about forty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "will",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know I left my phone on this table and it is not here now. Somebody ………………… it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must take",
                "must have taken",
                "can have taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That ………………… be true. She will never do something like that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can't",
                "shouldn't",
                "wouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………. him a fool. It really upset him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needn't call",
                "couldn't have called",
                "shouldn't have called"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor said I ………………. give up smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "can",
                "ought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… nicer to her. She really cares for you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can have been",
                "should have been",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you mind standing up for a moment?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was a bad place to go hiking. You …………………. your back.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should have broken",
                "could have broken",
                "should have broken"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Who is at the door?’ ‘It …………………. be the postman.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "could",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}